Lesson 25. Ted brings home more good news. Ted tells his family that a talent agent wants
to meet with him. The agent will fly Ted and Amber to New York. Nicole announces that
she's been named president of the Spanish Club. Amber and I are going to break into the
music business. Last night after our concert, a talent agent asks us to meet with him
in New York. Congratulations! We'll give you some spending money for your trip. No need. The
agent is putting the bill for everything. And when we get there, he's going to wine and
dynas. Wow, he must think you're the cream of the crop. He thinks we sound like the
Goo Goo Dolls. Who are they? You're really out of it. They're a popular rock band.
Our family is certainly on a winning streak. I was elected president of the Spanish Club today.
The Spanish Club? Big deal. You don't get it, Ted. This is only the beginning. Today,
president of the Spanish Club, tomorrow, ambassador to Spain. Well, ambassador, you'll need to
wrap up my chemistry homework before you leave for the Spanish Embassy. A rock star in a
diplomat. I'm so proud of both of you.